# Eren Dhoheiri

Jakarta Metropolitan Area



dhoheiri@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/erendhoheiri

# Summary

Lifetime-learner.

I'm learning programming by self-taught. So far I have HTML, CSS, Javascript under my belt for frontend development. I've started learning some serverside languages such as NodeJS, PHP, and Golang for backend development.

I'm still enthusiastically grabbing into any other programming languages, frameworks, or principles I can integrate into the coding apps into my head. I'm able to meet deadlines and high adaptability to changing priorities as evidenced by my experience in pursuing the world of programming as a professional developer.

My educational background gives me excellent analytics, problem-solving, managing resources, communication, and interpersonal skills with the ability to interact with individuals and work as part of a team.

# **Experience**



# 🏀 Software Engineer

### KOMPAS GRAMEDIA

Jul 2020 - Present (8 months +)

- Developing User Interface of Website based on given UI/UX design.
- Integrate between backend & frontend side.
- Work closely with Solution Analyst to fulfill the business needs.

Develop using Apostrophe CMS, MongoDB, NodeJS, and Nunjucks.

Areas: mykg.id, Paguyuban Purnakarya Kompas Gramedia, and Bentara Budaya Jakarta.

# **Application Developer**

### Celerates

2020 - Present (1 year 2 months +)

Celerates is solution provider for various industries in Indonesia that want to develop IT infrastructure, software development, and Business Intelligence.

As an application developer I'm responsible for:

- Develop and Maintain an Application for Client.
- Create, modify, and design custom apps for Clients.
- Support for Presales and Existing Project.

### Student Intern

### Domosquare

Sep 2018 - Nov 2018 (3 months)

Domosquare is the pioneer of hosting business in Indonesia. Domosquare provides quality affordable hosting and domains for all people, both individuals, and business institutions.

As student intern I'm responsible for:

- Fulfill tasks set out by supervisors from several departments.
- Perform research at a supervisor's request.
- Research and gather documentation on company position in the industry.

### **Education**



## Muhammadiyah University of Yogyakarta

Bachelor of Economic, Management 2015 - 2019

### **Licenses & Certifications**

JavaScript Essentials 2020 - Udemy: Online Courses UC-090c7043-bb08-4747-812f-a609c0c49790



React JS - A Complete Guide for Frontend Web Development - Udemy: Online Courses

UC-5d9e9eec-0e46-4c27-a57e-792f8b8c09de

Software Development Using Agile Methods - Udemy: Online Courses UC-f6c1717f-bc63-411f-8b6e-ae5792019fc

### **Skills**

Analytical Skills • Web Development • Problem Solving • Project Management • Programming • JavaScript • HTML • Python (Programming Language) • Git • PHP